A Guide to the Joseph Sobek Papers 1980.0039
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
- Series III: Geographical Files, circa 1958-1967
  - S. Pasadena, California—Sieban, G. (Box 12, Folder 332)
  - S. Williamsport, Pennsylvania—Pagana, J.A. (Box 12, Folder 333)
  - Spokane, Washington—YMCA (Box 12, Folder 334)
  - Springfield, Illinois
    - Myers Brothers (Box 12, Folder 335)
    - YMCA (Box 12, Folder 336)
  - Springfield, Massachusetts
    - Jewish Community Center (Box 12, Folder 337)
    - Springfield College (Box 12, Folder 338)
    - YMCA (Box 12, Folder 339)
  - St. John's—Greene, A.P.A. (Box 12, Folder 340)
  - St. Louis, Missouri
    - Jewish Community Center (Box 12, Folder 341)
    - YMCA (Box 12, Folder 342)
  - St. Peter, Minnesota—Gustavus Adolphus College (Box 12, Folder 343)
  - Stamford, Connecticut
    - Jewish Community Center (Box 12, Folder 344)
    - Stamford Racquetball (Box 12, Folder 345)
  - State College, Pennsylvania—Levine Brothers (Box 12, Folder 346)
  - Storrs, Connecticut
    - University of Connecticut (Athletics) (Box 12, Folder 347)
    - University of Connecticut (Library) (Box 12, Folder 348)
  - Syracuse, New York—Jewish Community Center (Box 12, Folder 349)
  - Tampa, Florida
    - First Baptist Church (Box 12, Folder 350)
    - YMCA (Box 12, Folder 351)
  - Tarrytown, New York—YMCA (Box 12, Folder 352)
  - Thomasville, Georgia
    - Kirby, Jack (Box 12, Folder 353)
    - YMCA (Box 12, Folder 354)
  - Tokyo, Japan—Shimizu Rubber Company (Box 12, Folder 355)
  - Toledo, Ohio (Box 12, Folder 356)
  - Toronto, Ontario
    - Broadview Branch (Box 12, Folder 357)
    - Holiday Tavern (Box 12, Folder 358)
  - Trenton, New Jersey
    - Trenton Club (Box 12, Folder 359)
    - YMCA (Box 12, Folder 360-361)
  - Traux Field, Wisconsin—Central Base Fund (Box 12, Folder 362)
  - Tucson, Arizona
    - Jewish Community Center (Box 12, Folder 363)
    - University of Arizona (Box 12, Folder 364)
    - YMCA (Box 12, Folder 365)
  - Tulsa, Oklahoma (Box 12, Folder 366)
  - Tyler, Texas—YMCA (Box 12, Folder 367)
  - Urbana, Illinois—University of Illinois (Box 12, Folder 368)
  - Utica, New York—YMCA (Box 12, Folder 369)
  - Vicksburg, Michigan—YMCA, Junius Ward Johnson (Box 13, Folder 370)
  - Victoria, Texas
    - Villareal, Manuel (Box 13, Folder 371)
    - YMCA (Box 13, Folder 372)
  - Waco, Texas—YMCA (Box 13, Folder 373)
  - Walla Walla, Washington—YMCA (Box 13, Folder 374)
  - Warren, Ohio—YMCA (Box 13, Folder 375)
  - Waterbury, Connecticut—YMCA (Box 13, Folder 376)
  - Watertown, New York—YMCA (Box 13, Folder 377)
  - West Hartford, Connecticut—Jewish Community Center (Box 13, Folder 378)
  - West Palm Beach, Florida—Hagyi, Gabriel (Box 13, Folder 379)
  - West Point, New York—U.S. Military Academy (Box 13, Folder 380)
  - West Springfield, Massachusetts—YMCA (Box 13, Folder 381)
  - Westerly, Rhode Island—YMCA (Box 13, Folder 382)
  - Westfield, Massachusetts—YMCA (Box 13, Folder 383)
  - White Plains, New York—YMCA (Box 13, Folder 384)
  - Wichita, Kansas
    - Excel Packing Company, Inc. (Box 13, Folder 385)
    - YMCA (Box 13, Folder 386)
  - Williams Air Force Base, Arizona (Box 13, Folder 387)
  - Williamsport, Delaware
    - Frymire Agency (Box 13, Folder 388)
    - Harder Sporting Goods (Box 13, Folder 389)
    - YMCA (Box 13, Folder 390)
  - Wilmington, Delaware—YMCA (Box 13, Folder 391)
  - Wilmington, North Carolina—YMCA (Box 13, Folder 392)
  - Winona, Minnesota
    - Kottke, Dick (Box 13, Folder 393)
    - St. Mary's College (Box 13, Folder 394)
  - Woonsocket, Rhode Island
    - Bancroft Comm. (Box 13, Folder 395)
    - YMCA (Box 13, Folder 396)
  - Worcester, Massachusetts—YMCA (Box 13, Folder 397)
  - Youngstown, Ohio
    - Jewish Federation (Box 13, Folder 398)
    - Thompson, Robert J. (Box 13, Folder 399)
- Series IV: Racquet and Ball, undated
  - Original paddle racquet (Box 14)
  - Original Joe Sobek paddle racquet ball